Guide to the Terence Sellers Papers 1967-2000 MSS.167
Fales Library and Special Collections
Terence Sellers Papers
1966-2013
Fales Library and Special Collections
MSS.167
49 Linear Feet 17 boxes from original donation; accretion in 6 record cartons and 1 flat oversized box; additional accretion in 22 record cartons, 4 oversize boxes, and 1 manuscript box
The Terence Sellers Papers include materials that relate to the art and literary scene in New York City in the 1970s and 1980s. The collection includes Sellers' writing, journals, photographs, and materials relating to her career as a professional writer.
Provenance
The Terence Sellers papers were purchased by the Fales Libary and Special Collections from Terence Sellers in 2005. In 2016 the estate of Terence Sellers donated two additions to the collection that comprise Series X. The accession numbers associated with these gifts are 2016.011 and 2016.025.
Biographical Note
Terence Sellers (1952-2016) was born to Robert and Gloria Sellers in Washington DC. From 1970-1973 she attended St. John's College in Santa Fe, New Mexico in the Classical Studies department but did not complete her degree. She earned a BA in forensic psychology at John Jay College in New York City in 1986.
In 1973 Sellers moved to New York City intending to pursue a career in writing and dance. Shortly after moving to New York she formed friendships with artists and writers including Anya Phillips, Kathy Acker, Duncan Smith, Victor Bockris, Carl Apfelschnitt, Jimmy De Sana and Duncan Hannah, many of which resulted in collaborations. For example, Sellers and Hannah worked on several projects together, including Amos Poe's 1978 film The Foreigner. Around the same time Sellers worked with photographer Jimmy De Sana on a series of 32 photographs entitled "The Dungeon Series". The original intent of the project was to use the photographs in Sellers' then unpublished work The Correct Sadist. However, after the work was complete De Sana and William S. Burroughs used the photographs to illustrate their own book project, Submission.
As a prolific writer, Sellers kept daily journals, maintained close correspondence with friends, family and colleagues, wrote a large volume of short stories and worked on several manuscripts. She was an early contributor to BOMB Magazine, X Magazine, Vacation and other publications devoted to New York's Downtown art, music, film and literary scene.
Most of Sellers' writing is on the subject of sadomasochism. While her work as a professional dominatrix and her fascination with violence, self-punishment, the occult, and psychoanalysis has given shape to much of her writing, her literary influences include Baudelaire, Dostoevsky, and the French surrealists.
Sellers' most famous work is a novel called the The Correct Sadist: The Memoirs of Angel Stern. It is written as a collection of short "case studies" relating to themes of sexual dominance and submission, bondage and discipline, and fetishism. Originally published by iKoo-Buchverlg in Berlin in 1981 as Der korrekte Sadismus, Sellers self-published the work in English under Vitriol Publications in 1983. In 1985, Grove Press contracted the novel and Barney Rosset handled its publication. It is also published in France, Italy, and the United Kingdom.
Sellers' other published novels include The Obsession, and Dungeon Evidence: The Correct Sadist II. Excerpts from other manuscripts such as The Degenerate, Most Ill of All and One Decadent Life have appeared in a wide range of publications in several languages. Sellers participated in events such as The Times Square Show (1980) and has read her work throughout the US, Europe and Canada. Although Sellers did not achieve the name recognition and literary success of some of her contemporaries, she is an important and influential member of the Downtown scene.
Scope and Content Note
The Terence Sellers Papers contain materials that relate to the literary career of Terence Sellers from the 1970's through the 1990's. Materials include journals, personal and professional correspondence, photographs, original artwork used in published works, manuscript materials, audio cassette recordings, and publicity materials relating to her published projects.
Arrangement
The Terence Sellers papers are organized into seven series:
Series I: Correspondence
Series II: Journals
Series III: Subject Files
Series IV: Writing
Series V: Photographic Materials
Series VI: Business
Series VII: Academic and Biographical Materials
Series VIII: Media
Series IX: Computer Disks
Series I: Correspondence and Series II: Journals have been arranged chronologically. Series III: Subject Files, Series IV: Writing, Series VI: Business and Series VII: Academic and Biographical Materials have been arranged alphabetically. Series V: Photographic Materials has been arranged alphabetically by photographer. Series VIII and XI have been retained in the order in which they were found.
Although they are physically separate, oversize materials are assigned folder numbers that reflect their place in the overall organization of the series. This is to indicate where they fall in the alphabetical or chronological order.
The Terence Sellers papers are organized into ten series:
Series I: Correspondence
Series II: Journals
Series III: Subject Files
Series IV: Writing
Series V: Photographic Materials
Series VI: Business
Series VII: Academic and Biographical Materials
Series VIII: Media
Series IX: Computer Disks
Series X: 2016 Accretion
Series I: Correspondence and Series II: Journals have been arranged chronologically. Series III: Subject Files, Series IV: Writing, Series VI: Business and Series VII: Academic and Biographical Materials have been arranged alphabetically. Series V: Photographic Materials has been arranged alphabetically by photographer. Series VIII and X have been retained in the order in which they were found.
Although they are physically separate, oversize materials are assigned folder numbers that reflect their place in the overall organization of the series. This is to indicate where they fall in the alphabetical or chronological order.
Missing Title
Series I: Correspondence
Series II: Journals
Series III: Subject Files
Series IV: Writing
Series V: Photographic Materials
Series VI: Business
Series VII: Academic and Biographical Materials
Series VIII: Media
Series IX: Computer Disks
Oversize - Series IV: Writing
Oversize - Series V: Photographic Materials
Oversize - Series VI: Business
Series X: 2016 Accretion
Related Material at Fales Library and Special Collections
Amos Poe Papers (unprocessed)
Jimmy De Sana Papers
Conditions Governing Access
Materials are open to researchers. Please contact the Fales Library and Special Collections, fales.library@nyu.edu, 212-998-2596.
Physical Characteristics and Technical Requirements
Access copies for some materials are available by appointment for reading room viewing and listening only. Please contact fales.library@nyu.edu, 212-998-2596.
Manuscripts for publication.; Photographs.; Grove Press.; Journals.; Audiotapes.; Correspondence.; Negatives (photographic); Etchings.; Sadomasochism |v Fiction.; New York (N.Y.) |v Fiction.; Sexual dominance and submission.; Books.; Clippings (information artifacts); Magazines (Periodicals); Sellers, Terence; De Sana, Jimmy; Poe, Amos; Phillips, Anya; P-Orridge, Genesis, 1950-; ikoo Buchverlag; Hannah, Duncan; Bretschneider, Jeffrey; Smith, Duncan; Acker, Kathy, 1948-1997; Apfelschnitt, Carl; V.I.T.R.I.O.L. Publications
- Series I: Correspondence
  Scope and Contents note
  This series consists of Terence Sellers' personal and business related correspondence from the 1970s through the 1990s, and includes snapshots, small mixed media drawings and paintings, and various printed materials. There is extensive correpondence between Sellers and Genesis P-Orridge, and Duncan Smith. The series also contains correspondence between Sellers and Kathy Acker, and others. Materials are organized chronologically by date, grouped by person or subject. Many folders include both correspondence to and from Sellers.
  - Correspondence to and from John Robert Sellers, Terence's father, 1970s (Box 1, Folder 1)
  - Correspondence from James Price, 1973 (Box 1, Folder 2)
  - Correspondence from John Sell, 1973 (Box 1, Folder 3)
  - Correspondence from Terence Sellers, 1972-1973 (Box 1, Folder 4)
  - Correspondence to and from John Robert Sellers, father, 1980s (Box 1, Folder 5)
  - Correspondence to family, 1980-1997 (Box 1, Folder 6)
  - Correspondence, January through July, 1980 (Box 1, Folder 7)
  - Correspondence, August through December, 1980 (Box 1, Folder 8)
  - Correspondence to and from Gerard Lemaire, 1980-1981 (Box 1, Folder 9)
  - Correspondence, January through May, 1981 (Box 1, Folder 10)
  - Correspondence, June through December, 1981 (Box 1, Folder 11)
  - The Correct Sadist: correspondence with printers, 1981 (Box 1, Folder 12)
  - Correspondence to and from Kathy Acker, 1980-1981 (Box 1, Folder 13)
  - Correspondence, January through May, 1982 (Box 1, Folder 14)
  - Correspondence, June through December, 1982 (Box 1, Folder 15)
  - Correspondence with Gerard Lemaire, 1982-1983 (Box 1, Folder 16)
  - Personal Correspondence, 1983 (Box 1, Folder 17)
  - General Correspondence, 1983 (Box 1, Folder 18)
  - The Correct Sadist: correspondence with Gerard Lemaire and publisher Christian Bourgois, 1983 (Box 1, Folder 19)
  - Correspondence to and from Genesis P-Orridge, 1983-1995 (Box 1, Folder 20)
  - Correspondence: V.I.T.R.I.O.L, Sarko and Sellers, 1983-1986 (Box 1, Folder 21)
  - The Correct Sadist: correspondence with IKoo Buchverlag, 1984 (Box 1, Folder 22)
  - Correspondence, January through May, 1984 (Box 1, Folder 23)
  - Correspondence, June through December, 1984 (Box 1, Folder 24)
  - Correspondence with Francois Peraldi, 1984 (Box 1, Folder 25)
  - Correspondence with Gerard Lemaire, 1984 (Box 1, Folder 26)
  - Correspondence, 1985 (Box 1, Folder 27)
  - Correspondence with IKoo Buchverlag, 1985-1989 (Box 1, Folder 28)
  - Correspondence, 1986 (Box 1, Folder 29)
  - Correspondence, January through August, 1987 (Box 1, Folder 29A)
  - Correspondence, September through December, 1987 (Box 1, Folder 30)
  - Correspondence from New Mexico, 1988 (Box 1, Folder 31)
  - Correspondence, January through May, 1988 (Box 1, Folder 32)
  - Correspondence, June through December, 1988 (Box 1, Folder 33)
  - Correspondence with Temple Press, 1988-1994 (Box 1, Folder 34)
  - Correspondence, January through May, 1989 (Box 1, Folder 35)
  - Correspondence, June through December, 1989 (Box 1, Folder 36)
  - Correspondence, January through May, 1990 (Box 2, Folder 37)
  - Correspondence, June through December, 1990 (Box 2, Folder 38)
  - Correspondence, January through May, 1991 (Box 2, Folder 39)
  - Correspondence, June through September, 1991 (Box 2, Folder 40)
  - Correspondence, January through May, 1992 (Box 2, Folder 41)
  - Correspondence, June through December, 1992 (Box 2, Folder 42)
  - Correspondence, January through May, 1993 (Box 2, Folder 43)
  - Correspondence, June through December, 1993 (Box 2, Folder 44)
  - Correspondence, January through May, 1994 (Box 2, Folder 45)
  - Correspondence, June through December, 1994 (Box 2, Folder 46)
  - Correspondence, January through April, 1995 (Box 2, Folder 47)
  - Correspondence, May through August, 1995 (Box 2, Folder 48)
  - Correspondence, September through December, 1995 (Box 2, Folder 49)
  - Correspondence, January through May, 1996 (Box 2, Folder 50)
  - Correspondence, June through December, 1996 (Box 2, Folder 51)
  - Correspondence January through May, 1997 (Box 2, Folder 52)
  - Correspondence, June through December, 1997 (Box 2, Folder 53)
  - Correspondence, Alexander, 1973 (Box 50, Folder 5)
  - Bob letters, Childhood/Autobiography, 1970-1980 (Box 50, Folder 11)
  - David Devincenzi letters, 1971-1974 (Box 50, Folder 12)
  - Carl Apfelschmitt, 1988-1989 (Box 50, Folder 29)
  - Duncan Smith, 1989-1991 (Box 50, Folder 30)
  - Correspondence, 1997 (Box 50, Folder 31)
  - Correspondence, 1995 (Box 50, Folder 32)
- Series II: Journals
  This series includes Sellers' journals that detail her personal life and professional life. Many of the journals also serve as early drafts for literary works and related to specific projects and subjects. Some journals also include clippings, photographs, and postcards.
  - Loose sheets from 1970's diaries (Box 2, Folder 54)
  - Journal, November through December, 1974 (Box 2, Folder 55)
  - Journal, December through February, 1974-1975 (Box 2, Folder 56)
  - Journal, February through November, 1975 (Box 2, Folder 57)
  - Journal, November, 1995 (Box 2, Folder 58)
  - Journal, "Commencing", November through March, 1975-1977 (Box 2, Folder 59)
  - Journal, "Thoth Tarot Card Readings", 1975 (Box 2, Folder 60)
  - Journal, June "NYC" through September "Paris", 1976-1979 (Box 2, Folder 61)
  - Journal, Venice and Paris, 1976-1977 (Box 2, Folder 62)
  - "Two Tiny Notebooks", 1976-1977 (Box 2, Folder 63)
  - "Occult Diary" January through July, 1977 (Box 2, Folder 64)
  - Journal, April through September, 1977 (Box 2, Folder 65)
  - Journal, October through October, 1977-1978 (Box 2, Folder 66)
  - Journal, March and June, 1978 (Box 3, Folder 67)
  - Journal, May through September, 1978 (Box 3, Folder 68)
  - Loose pages from diary, April, 1978 (Box 3, Folder 69)
  - Journal, September through February, 1978-1979 (Box 3, Folder 70)
  - Journal, February through July, 1979 (Box 3, Folder 71)
  - Journal, November through December, 1979 (Box 3, Folder 72)
  - Journal, May, 1981 (Box 3, Folder 73)
  - Journal, September through April, 1982-1983 (Box 3, Folder 73 A)
  - Journal, "London", December through August, 1982-1983 (Box 3, Folder 73 B)
  - Journal, "Junk Poll'd", June through December, 1983 (Box 3, Folder 73 C)
  - Go-Go Bookings, Diaries, Date Books, Planners, Calendars, Telephone Book, 1974-1994 (Box 50, Folder 14-21)
- Series III: Subject Files
  This series contains material that Sellers collected and organized that relates to specific literary projects and publications, subjects and events. Materials include journals, handwritten notes and correspondence, short stories and various printed materials.
  - Anya Phillips, 1977-1983 (Box 3, Folder 74)
  - Bataille Event, London, 1984 (Box 3, Folder 75)
  - BDSM, Printed Materials, 1970s (Box 3, Folder 76)
  - Books by Bob (Parody on her father, John Robert "Bob" Sellers), 1978-1980 (Box 3, Folder 77)
  - "Chris Parker: Cover of German Film Magazine", 1981 (Box 3, Folder 78)
  - "Christa and the Dragon", story based on life with Gordon Stevenson, 1980 (Box 3, Folder 79)
  - Clippings and notes on books to purchase, 1980s (Box 3, Folder 80)
  - Correspondence to American Psychological Association regarding Dr. Alan Levy, 1987 (Box 3, Folder 81)
  - "Death-Clinical Aspect", undated (Box 3, Folder 82)
  - Death-Inquisitions, 1972 (Box 3, Folder 83)
  - Dreams, undated (Box 3, Folder 84)
  - Dreams, 1971 (Box 3, Folder 85)
  - Dreams, 1972 (Box 3, Folder 86)
  - Dreams, 1973 (Box 3, Folder 87)
  - Dreams, 1974-1975 (Box 3, Folder 88)
  - Dreams, 1976-1977 (Box 3, Folder 89)
  - Dreams, 1980 (Box 3, Folder 90)
  - Duncan Hannah, undated (Box 3, Folder 91)
  - Duncan Smith: The Age of Oil, 1987 (Box 3, Folder 92)
  - Duncan Smith: The Age of Oil - Promotional files, undated (Box 3, Folder 92 A)
  - Duncan Smith, Works, undated (Box 3, Folder 92 B)
  - Essay on Carl Apfelschnitt, 1988 (Box 3, Folder 93)
  - F. Peraldi Essay of T.S. and Correct Sadist, c. 1980 (Box 3, Folder 94)
  - "Gordon Stevenson", journal, February to March, 1981 (Box 3, Folder 95)
  - Gordon Stevenson, writings, 1980 (Box 3, Folder 96)
  - "The Last of the Apfelschnitts", 1986 (Box 3, Folder 96 A)
  - "The Obsession, etchings project: Terence, Carl Apfelschnitt, psychiatrist, lawyers", 1986-1987 (Box 3, Folder 97)
  - Programs for plays and Concerts, 1973-1980 (Box 3, Folder 98)
  - Sadomasochism and Bondage, Printed Materials, 1980s (Box 3, Folder 98 A)
  - Sex and Language Congress, 1981 (Box 3, Folder 99)
  - "She, The Other": Francois Peraldi on Terence Sellers, c.1980 (Box 3, Folder 99 A)
  - "Skolimowski Interview - edited version/Q+A/LONG", 1979 (Box 3, Folder 99 B)
  - Suicide letters, undated (Box 3, Folder 100)
  - Suicide of Prostitutes, Printed Material, undated (Box 3, Folder 101)
  - "Tom Verlaine/ Obsession III", undated (Box 3, Folder 102)
- Series IV: Writing
  Series IV: Writings is divided into five subseries according to genre. Subseries A contains Sellers' short stories, poems and plays, organized alphabetically. Subseries B includes Sellers' novels, organized alphabetically by title. These materials also include research for each project including notes, manuscripts, drafts, proofs, and promotion and publication materials. Subseries C contains original artwork by Jeffrey Bretschneider and Carl Apfelschnitt that was produced to illustrate editions of her published work. Subseries D is a scrapbook that Sellers created of clippings from magazines and newspapers relating to her life and literary career. Subseries E includes copies of Sellers' published essays and prose works, including various editions of works. Original folders are also included with most of the work in this series because in many instances Sellers took notes and brainstormed on her original folders. All work is arranged alphabetically by project.
  - Subseries A: Short Stories, Poetry and Plays
    - "Aesthetic of the Perverse", undated (Box 3, Folder 103)
    - April 1972 (Box 3, Folder 104)
    - "The Attack of the Eyes", undated (Box 3, Folder 105)
    - "The Beloved", undated (Box 3, Folder 105 A)
    - "Beloved Mistress Here is the Corpse You Ordered", undated (Box 3, Folder 106)
    - "A Case of Moral Insanity", original envelope, undated (Box 3, Folder 107)
    - "A Case of Moral Insanity", rough draft, 1991-1994 (Box 3, Folder 108)
    - 'A Case of Moral Insanity", rough draft continued, 1991-1994 (Box 4, Folder 109)
    - "A Case of Moral Insanity", pages 1-25, 1994 (Box 4, Folder 110)
    - "A Case of Moral Insanity", pages 26-50, 1994 (Box 4, Folder 111)
    - "A Case of Moral Insanity", pages 51-65, 1994 (Box 4, Folder 112)
    - "Confessions of Mistress Severine", High Times, February 1979 (Box 4, Folder 113)
    - "Courage of the Crash: Shamanic Break", 1980 (Box 4, Folder 114)
    - "Details from the Life of a Fin-de-Siecle Author, Twentieth Century", undated (Box 4, Folder 115)
    - "Every Night A Fit", 1988 (Box 4, Folder 116)
    - "Fag Rag", published in Bomb, undated (Box 4, Folder 116 A)
    - "Fear of the Female Tormentor", 1978-1980s (Box 4, Folder 117)
    - "A Few Acid Writings", 1988 (Box 4, Folder 118)
    - "A Few Acid Writings, Reconstituted from a state of Celestial Apperception for Dull Human Consumption", published in Verbal Abuse #1 and Fenris Wolf (Sweden), 1988 (Box 4, Folder 118 A)
    - Notes and Review of Amos Poe's "The Foreigner, by Terens Severine" for NY Rocker, 1977 (Box 4, Folder 119)
    - "Forty Days and Forty Nights of Sexual Suicide", 1980 (Box 4, Folder 120)
    - "First Suicide/Childhood Trauma", undated (Box 4, Folder 121)
    - "Fragment From Childhood, Commencement of 'Myths'", undated (Box 4, Folder 122)
    - "The Gentleman Killers/Isabella", 1974 (Box 4, Folder 123)
    - "The Goddess on the Telephone/The Voice of Candy", 1988 (Box 4, Folder 124)
    - "Go-Go Girl Summer", 1974 (Box 4, Folder 125)
    - "The Hour of the Fey", published in Bomb, undated (Box 4, Folder 125 A)
    - "His Trust Violated", published in Vacation magazine, undated (Box 4, Folder 126)
    - "I Divine", 1981 (Box 4, Folder 127)
    - "I Want to be a Case History", undated (Box 4, Folder 127 A)
    - "L'Inconnue de la Seine" handwritten original, undated (Box 4, Folder 127 B)
    - "L'Inconnue de la Seine" inspiration text: Louis Aragon's Aurelien, 1946 (Box 4, Folder 127 C)
    - "Influence of Nietzsche: Essay-Genealogy of Morals", undated (Box 4, Folder 128)
    - "Inside One of the Best Little Whorehouses", 1979 (Box 4, Folder 129)
    - "It Was Not Nice of You Daddy-O", 1970s (Box 4, Folder 130)
    - "John Lennon--In Memoriam", 1980 (Box 4, Folder 131)
    - "Introduction to 13th Edition of Kraft Ebing's Psychopathia Sexualis", notebook, 1996 (Box 4, Folder 132)
    - "Introduction to 13th Edition of Kraft-Ebing Psychopathia Sexualis", draft, 1996 (Box 4, Folder 133)
    - "Introduction to 13th Edition of Kraft-Ebing Psychopathia Sexualis", draft - continued, 1996 (Box 4, Folder 134)
    - "Introduction to 13th Edition of Kraft-Ebing Psychopathia Sexualis", draft - continued, 1996 (Box 4, Folder 135)
    - "Introduction to 13th Edition of Kraft-Ebing Pyscholopathia Sexualis", original envelope with annotations., c. 2005 (Box 4, Folder 136)
    - "The Lesbian Child Molester", undated (Box 4, Folder 137)
    - "The Little Fountain", 1980 (Box 4, Folder 138)
    - "A Lost Manuscript of Donatien de Sade - 44 Moral Points", drafts, undated (Box 4, Folder 138 A)
    - "A Lost Manuscript of Donatien de Sade - 44 Moral Points", drafts - continued, undated (Box 4, Folder 138 B)
    - "A Lost Manuscript of Donatien de Sade - 44 Moral Points", 2006-2007 (Box 4, Folder 138 C)
    - "LSD/Mysticism" Article, 1979 (Box 4, Folder 139)
    - "LSD & Religious Fanaticism", published in High Times, 1979 (Box 4, Folder 139 A)
    - "The Marquesa d'Abiquiu", notebook, undated (Box 4, Folder 139 B)
    - "The Marquesa: A Play" pages 1-25, 1987 (Box 4, Folder 139 C)
    - "The Marquesa: A Play" pages 26-52, 1987 (Box 4, Folder 139 D)
    - "The Marquesa, Act I", 1987 (Box 4, Folder 139 E)
    - "The Marquesa, Acts II and III", 1987 (Box 4, Folder 139 F)
    - "Melancholy Methods of Cool-Keeping", 1979 (Box 4, Folder 140)
    - "Mistress Manslaughter" Drafts, undated (Box 4, Folder 141)
    - "Mistress Manslaughter" Drafts, continued, 1994 (Box 4, Folder 142)
    - "Mistress Manslaughter", published in Masquerade Magazine, 1998 (Box 4, Folder 143)
    - "Mistress Sterling and the Psychopath", journal, undated (Box 4, Folder 144)
    - "Mistress Sterling and the Psychopath", undated (Box 4, Folder 145)
    - "Most Ill of All" pages 1-29, 1994 (Box 4, Folder 146)
    - "Most Ill of All" pages 30-60, 1994 (Box 4, Folder 147)
    - 'Most Ill of All" copy, pages 1-55, 1994 (Box 4, Folder 148)
    - "Most Ill of All", bound copy, 1994 (Box 4, Folder 149)
    - "Introduction: Most Ill of All", c.1994 (Box 4, Folder 150)
    - "A Perculiarly Violent Day", 1980-1981 (Box 4, Folder 151)
    - "Perversion-Aesthetics", undated (Box 4, Folder 152)
    - "Perversion-Aesthetics" continued, undated (Box 5, Folder 153)
    - Poems--Handwritten, 1970s (Box 5, Folder 154)
    - Poems--Incomplete, 1970s (Box 5, Folder 155)
    - Poems--Typed, 1970s (Box 5, Folder 156)
    - "Poetry Roughs", 1970s (Box 5, Folder 157)
    - "Princess Perfect: A Play" pages 1-25, undated (Box 5, Folder 158)
    - "Princess Perfect: A Play" pages 26-50, undated (Box 5, Folder 159)
    - "Princess Perfect: A Play" pages 51-66, undated (Box 5, Folder 160)
    - "Princess Perfect", rough drafts, 1986 (Box 5, Folder 160 A)
    - "Psychological Survey of Clients" for article in Glamour Magazine (unpublished), 1986 (Box 5, Folder 161)
    - "Rhythms and Other Fragments", 1973 (Box 5, Folder 162)
    - "The Real Duncan", 1980/1993 (Box 5, Folder 163)
    - "The Real Duncan", undated (Box 5, Folder 164)
    - "Reluctantly Betrothed to Stan", 1988 (Box 5, Folder 165)
    - "Roads Poorly Taken", 1982 (Box 5, Folder 166)
    - "Sacher-Masoch Letter" and "To Achieve Death", 1989 (Box 5, Folder 167)
    - "Salo: 120 Days of Sodom", 1977 (Box 4, Folder 168)
    - "Shit on Heroin" drafts (Original title: "Still life with Dilaudid"), undated (Box 4, Folder 169)